{
    "id": "23c06cfb70654ad08cac8e4d42c254c5",
    "title": "Less and fewer",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5dd09bbe24584663b12b1aa32417c12d",
            "title": "Less And Fewer",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We did …………………. work today than yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He earns ………………….. than his wife.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You should learn to spend ………………….. money on stupid things.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You should spend …………………. time on the first task than on the second.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I answered ………………… questions than you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fewer",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The job was ………………….. difficult than I expected.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I got …………………. blackberries than her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fewer",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Try to make ………………….. mistakes when you write.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His latest book is …………………. interesting than his last one.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would buy that car if it were …………………. expensive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}